This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
How long have you been still?
I've been watching you the entire time.
You are one creepy guy.
Well, I really must say, I'm
surprised you decided to appear.
Did you think it was the
idle talk of a drunk?
You can hardly blame me
if I did, now can you?
When you're stuck in a cellar like this,
with gunpowder up your
nose for over twenty years,
you stop caring whether
or not talk is true.
So tell me, who am I hunting?
Oh yeah, I can feel the shivers.
Suddenly I remember why I've
been doing this all these years.
Be sure you show our master your
gratitude for keeping you here.
Hey!
I finally found you!
I've been looking for
you for a whole week.
I was told that you're rarely
open because you sell other stuff.
Well, besides boots, I mean.
Who knew?
Hey Sonny, you sure like to talk a lot.
I hope you like to talk
about boots for your sake.
I do.
But there's something else I want to know.
I'll abide by your rules.
I won't make any trouble.
Come on, what do you say?
Isn't this the most beautiful
day you've ever seen, Meryl?
Yes, it's beautiful.
It's the kind of day
that just makes you want
to sit here and forget
all about your problems.
Don't you agree?
Yes, definitely.
In fact, it makes you want to completely
forget about work and take the day off.
Not a chance, but nice try.
Shucks.
Get it over here!
The sky is unbelievably blue.
Hey, give me the ball!
No way!
There I go again.
Guess it's kind of stupid, huh?
I still keep thinking how
I'd like to show it to you,
even though that's no longer possible.
I just can't help myself.
Whoa, man!
I'm really, really sorry!
Are you okay, mister?
The deadly dodgeball head!
A simple technique to hold the
ball in place with intense suction!
Try this at home, kids!
Hey, it's Mr. Bash!
What in the hell is that man doing?
Isn't it wonderful, Meryl?
Huh?
That the Vash we know and love is back!
Have you gone insane?
What are you talking about?
All right, guys, who wants ice cream, huh?
Are you treating?
All right!
Get six, okay?
But why do you want six of them?
Isn't that one too many?
One is for her.
Here you go.
We've got a ball.
You want to come and play?
Wait, where are you going?
We're over here, honey.
We're over here.
Here it goes!
Hey, mister! Over here! I'll get him out!
I found you, Vash the Stampede.
What?
Who are you?
Legato.
Legato Blue Summers.
Mr. Vash? Hmm?
Well, uh, it's n-nothing.
Ah!
Hey, lady!
Corée! Coming!
What was that strange look on his face?
It was frightening.
What do you want from me?
You're alive.
Perhaps that was a bit too dramatic.
Actually, I'm here as a messenger.
That's right.
I've come here to warn you.
I'm afraid your life
is going to end today.
What?
Do you think I'm lying to me?
I haven't given you a gift yet, have I?
Your reaction was better than I hoped.
You're fun.
And to think I could kill every man,
woman, and child here in the
blink of an eye if I wanted to.
The power of death is intoxicating.
Don't be in so much of a hurry.
You still have a little time left.
Or, perhaps you don't.
And don't worry, no one
else needs to get hurt.
So do you want to draw.
Oh, I almost forgot.
This is a little farewell gift.
It contains a lesson from me.
I'll just leave it here.
Help me!
What's up with her?
That's a shoemaker's wife.
Wow, she looks really upset.
Hey! It's murder!
It's okay, calm down. Murder?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
My husband!
My husband's in there, but he won't talk!
He can't say anything!
I'm sorry, but I can't
seem to understand you!
What are you trying to say?
He won't talk!
He won't say a word!
My husband!
Sheriff, he didn't do it!
He's innocent!
Save it for the judge to decide,
lady, this is not a courthouse.
Listen, we have witness testimony
that places him at the shoe store.
He also just happened to be the one
closest by when the owner's body was found.
And we've got evidence.
What's more,
we ran a check and found
out he's that humanoid
typhoon everyone's been
talking about lately.
I'd have to be completely out of
my mind not to lock up that guy.
Now, if I were to cut him loose and
he was to make off into the night,
would you take the heat?
I think not.
It's a little farewell gift.
I'll just leave it here.
I'm afraid your life
is going to end today.
What does he want from me?
A 60 billion double dollar reward?
No.
Is it him?
Oh, hey, Vash.
Um, Mr. Vash?
Oh, hi.
Is everything all right here?
Oh, it's just you.
Uh-huh. Oh, Vash!
I'm so sorry about all of this, but will
you please stay here just for today?
We'll come for you tomorrow, I promise.
That's nice, thank you.
But don't go out of
your way from me, okay?
As far as I know, you're innocent
and haven't done anything wrong.
I need some time alone to think right now.
Um, hey, Mr. Vash? Yes?
Well, uh, actually, actually it's nothing!
What does that mean, Millie?
Actually, it means nothing!
What?
What was that?
Get down!
Thanks for showing me in.
Can you hear me, Vash the Stampede?
My name is Monev the Gale,
and I'm here to send you to
hell just as you were promised.
Both of you, run!
What's going on here?
Get out while you can!
The enemy is coming!
Hurry!
What do you mean by the enemy?
Who is he and what is he doing here?
this was simple simple
enough to make me realize
I've been wasting my life
let go of him right now
why do you have any idea
how long 20 years is
imprisoned in that
disgusting place with nothing
to do but physical
training it was like living
in the bowels of hell
but once I kill you those
days of torture will be over forever.
Five clicks into the end.
Four. Three. Two. One.
Why you?
It's true what I was told about this guy.
He's a complete chicken shit.
Uh, Mira? What are you doing?
We should go after him.
Uh, something's wrong with Bash.
What?
The way he's been acting.
What? What happened?
Looks like somebody attacked
the sheriff's office.
Was it Prince of that guy in
jail trying to set him free?
Stay away from me!
Run for your lives!
Coming through!
Whatever you do, don't get near me!
Take cover until I'm safely out of town!
I'm not kidding.
It's a matter of life and death here.
It's the guy!
Vash, a stampede!
I said sit down!
I'm sorry for it!
No people!
You know that pinhead
arrogant little twerk?
Does he actually think he can get
away from me and keep up this pace?
Run!
Run or I'll shoot!
Yeah, run, hot shot, whatever you say.
You idiots, I warned you!
Still helping others
even at a time like this?
You are weak.
If you have any expectations of staying
alive, you better use them as a shield.
But don't worry, it'll
all be over soon anyway.
Now's the end of Vash the Stampede!
You and this town die together!
Oh, my God.
I did it!
So much for the legendary
outlaw! He was nothing!
He died like a coward! At last!
At last I'm free!
Now I can live the way I want to live!
Ah...
This...
this must be a nightmare.
Those eyes...
It's like looking in
the eyes of the Diablo!
He did go this way, didn't he?
Yes.
Mr. Vash!
Stay back!
Stay away from me.
Who is he?
That's not Vash.
That is not the same man.
He's walking away.
If we let him leave now, he'll
probably never come back.
I don't think we can stop him.
The way he's acting?
I don't think anyone
can stop him right now.
I can't believe the way he shot at me.
Isn't he supposed to be so spineless
that he's unable to kill a fly?
He was like the devil himself.
He's shown his true nature to me.
But I still have to take his life.
I have no choice.
Wait! Wait! What do you want?
I need to use your safe.
Open it.
But, sir, I can't... I...
I... Hurry! There's no time!
Two shots left.
How can I do this?
I see your plan.
You're gonna use the big safe as a shield.
I'll mutilate you!
Along with that vault door!
You have no more bullets, coward!
Ah, a hidden gun.
Why didn't he use it before?
He could have shot me then.
You'll pay.
You will pay for this!
They're dead.
The people are dead.
Who the hell cares?
You killed all the people!
You killed them all!
And you are the ones solely
responsible for all their deaths!
Now you are also going to die!
Don't kill me!
Please!
I'm sorry!
I don't wanna die!
I don't wanna die! Please!
Don't kill me! Oh no!
I don't wanna die!
Are you awake now?
Yeah but I was dreaming
rem everything everything
was so horribly dry even people's hearts
From far away as I watched
the people who lived there I
always found myself wondering
How and why could they possibly
keep on living what motivation
did they have that Would get
them up every day no matter
what for the rest of their lives
It's just that you're always so
serious even when you're dreaming
You'll turn into an
old man very quickly if
you keep on constantly
pondering like that I'm
excited to think that
the ticket I was handed
on the day of my birth was completely open
The choices we make in life
have unlimited possibilities
All I can do is think about them.
This is all I can do.
Oh, Vash, no.
If I...
If I shot him now,
you really would die.
It would be wrong to shoot him, right?
The blue sky in the middle of the
sky, the wind is in the future.
The light of the sky,
as you can see the
light of the sky!
Routine Report, date July Thou.
Two days after the incident
caused by a man named Monev,
tension still runs high in the city.
The events that occurred there made
me realize something all over again.
It's an awareness which becomes obscured
as I keep regular contact with him.
That being, the reason Vash the
Stampede is called the Humanoid Typhoon.
Yet I still don't understand.
Why is it that so much trouble
falls into this man's lap?